Now a unit test government could look like this.
Uh, you know, where you have listed down different, uh,
unit test cases like the, the count of records.
Is it valid or not?
Whether, uh, this field right here is
per this logic or not.
So for all the different fields you see here,
you have unit test cases along with, as I said, the count
of, uh, the records as well.
And you'll also be doing unit testing for, uh,
data quality tools as well by checking whether, okay,
do we have any data, uh, which
actually matches this condition?
Okay? Our intent was to rigid the records.
So do we have any records which actually
satisfies these conditions
and have somehow nicked into our curated data set or not?
If they have, it means the unit test cases has failed
that particular, okay?
So essentially, for example, you'll,
you'll probably do a threat staff on the table
where trip miles ease greater than 500.
You get the point. And if it is, if you find any records
that test case fails
and your code is incorrect,
you're gonna go back and fix the code.
That is what is mean by unit testing. Okay?
So now what I wanna do next, you wanna hand, as I said,
you'll be handling over the code to the data analyst, right?
So they may not have access to the tables.
So you ask the cloud engineer team to provide access
to the curated HF H-V-F-H-V table for the data analyst
for them to do their analysis.
Okay? Now that part is done.
Now you have lower the data for two years integrated a lake
in curated layer.
You have the table built already. So what's the next step?
Next step is to now think about
loading the data from curated
to the aggregated layer, right?
And for that, you already have the mapping. Okay?
Now you start analyzing this.
You, you wanna understand this right?
As to what is happening here.
I mean, this, this looks pretty overwhelming for anybody.
In fact, so many columns, so many, so many rows here.
Simple thing. Put this in the VS code.
Ask in Q to analyze it for you.
It'll tell you exactly what is happening here,
but that, that is kind of your resistant to help you
with what is happening here, right?
So now you understand, okay, that the analysts are asking us
to group by based on all of these fields you see here.
And there are some aggregations that they're asking us.
And if we scroll down, uh, you have more
fields on which you wanna group by.
So that's a lot of fields on which they want,
they're asking us to group by.
So you are trying to kind
of make sense of what is happening here.
And then meanwhile, the analysts are also analyzing the data
that you have already curated.
And when you're about to really, uh, start developing this,
they got back to you and they said, no.
Hey, hold on. We have an updated mapping sheet.
So they gave you this mapping sheet
that they say we have analyzed the data and q it
and you know, for our business need,
I think this is these, uh, three
Different aggregations make more sense than having just
one aggregated, uh, layer.
Okay? So this would've given us just one table,
one aggregated table.
Now we could actually come up with, you know, three tables,
which will help our business use cases, what they say.
And now, okay, finally, okay?
And then, then you kind of take a look at this.
Uh, you try to make sense of this here.
Yes, we have table one. Okay?
You wanna make a big by based on these dimensions.
And then you have the aggregations, uh, defined here.
And then they've also mentioned them use
case for you to understand them.
And similarly, for table two as well,
and, uh, table three as well, you have, uh,
the mappings defined here.
Okay? So based on this, you can now go ahead
and build your next, uh, jobs
towards the next step to kind
of create the code in a glue notebook, right?
So that is what we'll do in the next step.